Welcome back to the Amanda Seals show.
And I am joined, I'm joined right here by sexually active DJ Nails.
Oh, damn.
Who this story would apply to.
You know, this story right here is relevant to you.
You are a single man who's out here having a good time on the weekend.
And experimental male birth control has been proven effective and it prevents pregnancy.
They actually did this test right here with some mice, right?
And listen to this.
It's a non-hormonal contraceptive drug that was found to disable sperm in male mice by researchers Will Cornell Medical College in NYC.
I honestly believe this is going to make STD rates jump, Amanda.
Yeah, I can see that, right?
Because cats would be like, well, all right, you can't get pregnant.
But, you know, if you go to a little burn or something, I can just take a pill and get rid of that.
Like, I feel like that's what will end up happening.
But as we talked about previously, there's a whole syphilis outbreak happening in Mississippi right now.
Because clearly people are already not paying enough attention to slowing the spread of STDs.
Like there's like a whole gonorrhea strain that is not being responsive to penicillin.
So like, don't let this get you in a burning situation that doesn't stop burning.
Can I trust that the man gon' take it?
That's the thing.
I don't know.
Like a dridelisin.
Thank you.